<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.11</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 3.1.1.50 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://pad.asp-software.org</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>pluck-n-play</Company_Name>
		<Address_1>Meißner and Meißner GbR</Address_1>
		<Address_2>Franz-Gresitza-Str. 64</Address_2>
		<City_Town>Jena</City_Town>
		<State_Province />
		<Zip_Postal_Code>07749</Zip_Postal_Code>
		<Country>Germany</Country>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.pluck-n-play.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>Andreas</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Meißner</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>am@pluck-n-play.com</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Andreas</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Meißner</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>contact@pluck-n-play.com</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>sales@pluck-n-play.com</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>support@pluck-n-play.com</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>contact@pluck-n-play.com</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone>+49-3641-354910</Sales_Phone>
			<Support_Phone>+49-3641-354910</Support_Phone>
			<General_Phone>+49-3641-354910</General_Phone>
			<Fax_Phone>+49-3641-358536</Fax_Phone>
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>Chord Scale Generator</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.3</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>08</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>21</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2012</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>30</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code>EUR</Program_Cost_Other_Code>
		<Program_Cost_Other>21.95</Program_Cost_Other>
		<Program_Type>Demo</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>No Install Support</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Linux</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English,German</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info>Extended Lists of Instruments and Scales; Improved Import and Export Features</Program_Change_Info>
		<Program_Specific_Category>Audio</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class>Audio &amp; Multimedia::Music Composers</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_System_Requirements>1 GHz CPU, 256 MByte RAM, 50 MByte HD</Program_System_Requirements>
		<File_Info>
			<File_Size_Bytes>39146756</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>38229</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>37.33</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count />
			<Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
			<Expire_Other_Info />
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>chord generator, chord finder, scale finder, chords, guitar chords, ukulele chords, banjo chords, mandolin chords, chord chart, chord book, scales, guitar scales, bass scales, pentatonics, stringed instrument</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>chord generator, chord finder, scale finder</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>chord generator, chord finder and scale finder for guitar, ukulele, and more</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Chord generator, chord finder and scale finder for guitar, bass, ukulele, banjo, mandolin, or any other stringed instrument. Visualizes results of calculations on a fretboard, a keyboard as well as in musical notation, chord charts and tablatures.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Chord Scale Generator features a chord generator, chord finder and scale finder. Results of calculations are visualized on a fretboard, a keyboard, in musical notation, chord charts and tablatures. Rather than building on a limited database, generic algorithms are used to enable calculations for any tuning or stringed instrument such as guitar, ukulele, banjo or mandolin. Various export features help to create individual scale and chord books.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>The Chord Scale Generator features a chord generator, chord finder and scale finder and thus enables various interesting calculations around chords and scales. This software tool helps you to find all possible chord charts (including fingerings) for each chord. It is also possible to perform the reverse calculation and find corresponding chords to a certain chord chart, fingering pattern or musical notation. As well, you can find matching scales to a melody or riff.
Results of calculations are visualized in graphical views such as a fretboard or a keyboard. Furthermore, chords and scales are presented in musical notation, chord charts and tablatures.
Rather than building on a statical limited database the Chord Scale Generator uses generic algorithms to enable calculations for any tuning or stringed instrument. The software supports all instruments with 2 to 12 strings (or doubled strings) such as guitar, bass, ukulele, banjo or mandolin as well as more exotic instruments like charango, bouzouki, balalaika, domra or cavaquinho. The usage of generic algorithms also allows for the individual extension of the program with additional chord and scale definitions.
The Chord Scale Generator provides settings for left handed players. It is also possible to define if you play the instrument as a lefty or righty.
The graphical representations of chords and scales can be exported to other applications via the clipboard or as image files. Therefore, the Chord Scale Generator supports the creation of individual scale, song and chord books.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
		<German>
			<Keywords>Chord Generator, Chord Finder, Scale Finder, Akkorde, Gitarrenakkorde, Grifftabellen, Gitarrengriffe, Skalen, Tonleiter, Pentatonik, Gitarre, Ukulele, Banjo, Mandoline, Bass, Saiteninstrument</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Berechnungen rund um Akkorde und Skalen</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Berechnungen und Darstellungen zu Grifftabellen, Akkorden und Skalen (Tonleiter)</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Ermöglicht Berechnungen rund um Akkorde und Skalen (Tonleitern) für Gitarre, Ukulele, Banjo oder jedes andere Saiteninstrument. Ergebnisse werden auf einem Griffbrett, einer Klaviatur, als Grifftabelle, Tabulatur und in Notenschreibweise dargestellt.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Der Chord Scale Generator ermöglicht verschiedene Berechnungen rund um Akkorde und Skalen (Tonleitern). Die Ergebnisse werden auf einem Griffbrett, einer Klaviatur sowie als Grifftabellen, Tabulaturen und in Notenschreibweise dargestellt. Durch Verwendung generischer Algorithmen anstelle einer statischen Datenbank können alle Saiteninstrumente (Gitarre, Bass, Ukulele, Banjo, ...) sowie beliebige Akkord- und Skalendefinitionen unterstützt werden.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Der Chord Scale Generator ermöglicht verschiedene Berechnungen rund um Akkorde und Skalen (Tonleitern). Die Ergebnisse werden auf einem Griffbrett, einer Klaviatur sowie als Grifftabellen, Tabulaturen und in Notenschreibweise dargestellt.
Die Software hilft dabei, alle Griffmöglichkeiten für einen Akkord zu finden oder in einer umgekehrten Berechnung zu einem Griff- oder Notenbild die dazugehörigen Akkorde zu ermitteln. Zudem ist es möglich, sich passende Skalen zu einer Melodie bzw. einem improvisierten Lauf bestimmen zu lassen.
Anstelle einer limitierten statischen Datenbank verwendet der Chord Scale Generator generische Algorithmen. Die Software kann somit für sämtliche Saiteninstrumente und Instrumentenstimmungen eingesetzt werden. So unterstützt der Chord Scale Generator alle Saiteninstrumente mit 2 bis 12 Einzel- oder Doppelsaiten, also Instrumente, wie Gitarre, Bass, Ukulele, Banjo oder Mandoline, aber auch exotischere Instrumente wie Charango, Bouzouki, Balalaika, Domra oder Cavaquinho. Die Verwendung generischer Algorithmen erlaubt zudem die individuelle und uneingeschränkte Erweiterung der Anwendung um zusätzliche Akkord- und Skalendefinitionen.
Der Chord Scale Generator berücksichtigt zudem Linkshänder sowie das Spielen von Lefty- und Righty-Instrumenten.
Es ist möglich, sämtliche grafischen Darstellungen (Griffbrett, Klaviatur, Grifftabellen, Tabulaturen und Notenbilder) von Akkorden und Skalen als Bilddatei sowie über die Zwischenablage in andere Anwendungen zu exportieren. Somit ermöglicht der Chord Scale Generator die Erstellung eigener Akkord-, Skalen- und Liederbücher.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</German>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://www.pluck-n-play.com</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>http://www.pluck-n-play.com/en/buy.html</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.pluck-n-play.com/en/screenshots/linux/chord_generation.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>http://www.pluck-n-play.com/images/csg.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.pluck-n-play.com/pad/csg_lin.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>http://www.pluck-n-play.com/data/CSG-linux-gtk.tar.gz</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL>http://www.pluck-n-play.com/data/CSG-linux-gtk_64.tar.gz</Secondary_Download_URL>
			<Additional_Download_URL_1 />
			<Additional_Download_URL_2 />
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions>Contact contact@pluck-n-play.com for distribution agreements.</Distribution_Permissions>
		<EULA>END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT

Licensor:

Meißner &amp; Meißner GbR 
Andreas Meißner, Mathias Meißner 
Franz-Gresitza-Str. 64 
07749 Jena
Germany

IMPORTANT - READ CAREFULLY. NOTICE TO USER:

THIS END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT (EULA) IS A LEGAL DOCUMENT BETWEEN YOU AND THE GBR ANDREAS MEIßNER AND MATHIAS MEIßNER (MEIßNER &amp; MEIßNER GBR). IT IS IMPORTANT THAT YOU READ THIS DOCUMENT BEFORE USING THE CHORD SCALE GENERATOR (“SOFTWARE”) AND ANY ACCOMPANYING DOCUMENTATION. THE DOWNLOAD, INSTALLATION AND USE OF THE SOFTWARE IS SUBJECT TO THE GRANT OF LICENSE INCLUDED HEREIN AND IS SUBJECT TO AND RESTRICTED AS SET FORTH BELOW.

1. Authorized Users; Authorized Use

The Software may only be downloaded, installed or used by (i) the owner of the computer on which the software is downloaded and installed (the "Authorized Computer"), and (ii) any persons authorized by the owner of the Authorized Computer to use the Authorized Computer and to download and install the software in accordance with this EULA, provided that the individuals referred to in (i) and (ii) above have read this EULA and agree to abide by it before any such download or installation and at all times while using the software.

The right to issue licenses for the full version of the software, remain to Meißner &amp; Meißner GbR only. These licenses are 'Single Computer Licenses'. A 'Single Computer License' is a non-transferable license, which permits the customer to use the full version of software product on a single computer. Duplication, sharing, multiple installations and/or electronic transmission of this license are in violation of this contract and international conventions copyright. Besides, you ar not permitted to rent, lease or lend out the software. With a valid activation key, the software may be activated on a single computer workstation. If the customer later wants to install the software on a different workstation, the customer must purchase additional licenses.

We hereby agree to grant to you, a non-exclusive, limited license, to download, install and use the most recent version of the software subject to the provisions set forth in this EULA. We may, but need not, issue software changes, patches and fixes (collectively, "updates") to the software. If and when we issue updates to the software to the general public or otherwise, we may, but are not required to, make such updates available to you. The software shall include such updates and the updated software shall be governed by the terms of this EULA.

2. Restrictions

The use of the software is subject to the following additional restrictions: You are prohibited from (i) decompiling, reverse engineering, or disassembling the software, or otherwise attempting to derive their source code; (ii) tampering or interfering with the functionality, delivery or operation of the software while using or installing it, (iii) selling, renting, transferring, reselling, or distributing the software to any third party; (iv) duplicating, reproducing, copying (except for reasonable backup purposes), modifying, or otherwise creating derivative works of the software, or (v) exporting or re-exporting the software, directly or indirectly, into any country prohibited by law.

3. Ownership of Intellectual Property

You agree that nothing contained herein entitles you to own the software. You hereby agree and acknowledge that as between you and us, we (or Third Parties) own all right, title and interest in and to the software, and in and to any intellectual property (including without limitation, copyrights, patents, trademarks, and any other proprietary rights) included in or applicable to the software. If you send us or otherwise share with us any ideas, comments, or suggestions regarding the software, you acknowledge and agree that we may use such ideas, comments or suggestions in any manner, for any purpose, and without the need for any further compensation, approval or consent. You also hereby agree to assign to us all right, title and 
interest in and to any such ideas, comments or suggestions.

4. Disclaimer of Warranties

We disclaim any responsibility for any harm resulting from your download, installation, use or uninstallation of the software. The software are provided “as is”, with no warranties of any kind. To the maximum extent permitted by law, we fully disclaim all express, implied and statutory warranties, including, without limitation, the warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement. We do not warrant that the software will be operable, or that their operation will be uninterrupted or error free or that the software will function or operate in conjunction with any other product, software or hardware, or that the software will not dame any other product, software or hardware or cause any loss or corruption of data, or will have a minimum service life.

This disclaimer of warranties may not be allowed in certain jurisdiction, so the provisions of this section may not apply to you.

5. Limitation of Liability

In no event will we be liable to you for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, consequential, exemplary or punitive damages arising out of or in connection with your download, installation, use or misuse, uninstallation, or reliance upon the software, whether such liability arises from any claim based upon contract, warranty, tort (including negligence), product liability, personal injury, trespass to chattels or otherwise, and whether or not the person causing such loss or damage has been advised of the possibility of such loss or damage. Some jursidiction limit the availability of such limitations of liability, in which case the provisions of this section may not apply to you. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in no event shall our liability exceed $50.

6. Miscellaneous

This agreement is exclusively governed by the laws of the Federal Republic of Germany excluding the United Nations convention on the international sale of goods (CISG). The only place of jurisdiction is Jena in the Federal Republic of Germany, provided that the customer is a businessman. The supplier is additionally entitled to take action at the place of the customer's place of general jurisdiction.

The German version of this EULA as set out here take precedence over translations into other languages in case of doubt.

Changes and supplements must be made in writing. This also applies to the written form clause.

The ineffectiveness of one or several provisions made in this agreement does not affect the effectiveness of the remainder of this agreement. An ineffective provision will be replaced by an effective one, which is adjusted such as to be as close as possible to the economic purpose of the original ineffective clause.

This EULA, together with any non-conflicting portions of the General Terms and Conditions, collectively constitute the entire agreement between you and us with respect to your download, installation, use and uninstallation of the software, and supersede and replace all prior or contemporaneous understandings or agreements, written or oral, regarding such subject matter.

Any changes that we make to this EULA will be posted at http://www.pluck-n-play.com/en/license.html. Your use of the software will always be governed by the EULA in effect at the time of use.

Meißner &amp; Meißner GbR
Andreas Meißner, Mathias Meißner
Franz-Gresitza-Str. 64, 07749 Jena, Germany

January 2009</EULA>
	</Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
